Tomas Roy

Carrboro, NC

About Me

After 8 years in the web & software development industry, I'm excited about work opportunities that are different: work that is local, relies on workplace community, and involves active face-to-face communication and physical activity. I am motivated by diversity of experience, relationships and human interaction more than I am by compensation.

Work Experience

Roof / Co-founder & Software Developer

August 2015 - April 2018

I worked with a small team of developers and designers to create a multi-platform application for housemates and property managers. My technical experience includes web-based & mobile software development (Angular JS & Android), back-end software development (Node JS), Git Hub, UNIX and more. My professional experience includes customer experience design, customer service, complex problem solving, and team communication and consensus.

MiniCreative / Freelance Web Developer

November 2010 - April 2018

I provide website design and development services for over 45 clients. My experience includes HTML/CSS/JS/PHP development, Photoshop/Illustrator design work, project consulting, proactive client communication, invoicing and accounting. My portfolio is available at minicreative.net

Omni Montessori School / Groundskeeper & Childcare Assistant

March 2013 - May 2014

My experience includes pond, garden and lawn maintenance, interactive child-care, food preparation and cleaning.

Waxhaw Swim & Racquet Club / Lifeguard

April 2011 - September 2012

My experience includes certified lifeguarding, opening & closing routines, food preparation, and cleaning.

Education

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill / Computer Science &

Philosophy (BA)

2014 - 2018 / 3.7 GPA

UNC Tramping Club President, Launch Chapel Hill Startup Development Cohort

_

Camp SOAR / Special Olympics Camp Counselor

Volunteer Experience

2010 - 2013

I volunteered annually as a one-on-one camp counselor for special needs athletes during a sports-oriented summer camp.

Missionaries of the Poor / Volunteer

2012 - 2014

I volunteered weekly at a community outreach organization, helping with child-care, activity leadership, and meal preparation.